Guide to the Yale School of Music Faculty Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale School of Music faculty records
1886-1972
RU 463
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.5
(4 boxes)
The records consist of personnel files documenting faculty of the Yale School of Music.
Yale School of Music
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 28-A (YRG 28-A), Central records and records of the dean of the Yale School of Music.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the School of Music, 1972.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of personnel files documenting faculty of the Yale School of Music.
Arrangement
The records are arranged alphabetically by last name.
College teachers; Yale School of Music; Yale University -- Faculty
- Faculty personnel records, 1886-1972; Accession 1973-A-003
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2048
  - Brown, George, 1935-1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Browne, Richard Joseph, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cecil, Robert M., 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Connolly, Justin R., 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cooke, Judd, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Crocker, Richard, 1946-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Einstein, Alfred, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fuchs, Joseph, 1952-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Garfield, Bernard, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gushee, Marion, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hughes, David G., 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Jacobson, George Hartrig, 1942-1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Kenney, Sylvia Wisdom, 1945-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Knight, Henry Stanley, 1886-1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kortschak, Hugo [University Orchestra], 1923-1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kraehenbuehl, John David, 1946-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Liepmann, Klaus, 1941-1947 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Linsley, Ralph E., 1925-1945 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Loach, Donald, 1950-1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Lockwood, Nomand, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - McChesney, Ernest, 1954-1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mowe, Homer G., 1946-1956 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Pease, L. F., 1919-1932 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Perle, George, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Porter, Quincy, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Rappeport, Phyllis, 1958-1964 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Rogers, Francis, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Schrade, Leo, 1938-1964 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Seeger, Charles, 1943-1950 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Silva, Lufgi, 1951-1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Sloane, Wesley, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Smith, David Stanley - articles and reports re: Music School, 1929-1937 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Smith, David Stanley - correspondence, 1927-1956 (Box 3, Folder 33 - 34)
  - Stesrns, Peter Pindar, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Stevens, Halsey, 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Stoeber, Ernmerman, 1925-1946 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Tenney, James C., 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 38 - 39)
  - Troostwyk, Isidore Mrs., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Videro, Finn, 1958-1965 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Von Heereman, Marianna, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Waith, Margaret D. [Mrs. Eugene], 1945-1958 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Winternitz, Emmanuel, 1949-1952 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Wolfe, Robert E., 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 45)